Galgal Channel GOGO
I would like to take packing videos!
I'm going to Okinawa for two days and one night starting tomorrow.
I'm going to Okinawa for two days and one night tomorrow.
But it's 12:20 at night, so I'm going to do it at home.
I'll do it at home with the light burning in a whisper.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be in a music program called "Music comer" today.
It's the day of the show.
Look at me, I'm a little sparkly.
And I put on some makeup and looked cute.
I'm still the same.
I have an early flight tomorrow morning.
I can fly to Okinawa on an early flight tomorrow morning.
I'm so excited.
If I don't hurry, I won't have time to sleep.
I'm going to start preparing as soon as possible.
I have some things
I'd like to introduce them to you.
It's a two day and one night trip
I've prepared clothes for the second day.
The second day we are going to eat and walk around.
I thought I would take a lot of pictures, so I thought about it...
I'm going to wear a pair of shorts and a beige tank top like this one.
I'm sure some of you have seen me in this outfit before, but........I'm sure some of you have seen me all the time, or maybe you've seen me a lot.
Wearing this white vest
Here is the item I definitely wanted to use in Okinawa.
Here it is!
Ta-da!
I bought this tie a few years ago, and I thought it was really cute and I wanted to use it, but I thought it would be a little difficult to use in everyday life.
I thought it would go well with Okinawa, so I decided to use it as a regular necktie and I've been seeing it a lot lately, so I thought I'd share it with you.
I wonder if it's a fad? This is how you wear it.
I think I'm basically a person who carries a lot of baggage.
I'm the type of person who likes to carry a lot of spare parts.
I heard a rumor that you can swim in the pool in Okinawa.
So I will bring my swimsuit.
Here is my swimsuit!
It's a rash guard and pants that I specially prepared when I went on a trip a long time ago!
I like it because it's nothing out of the ordinary!
Put this in a bag.
Isn't it cute?
I'm taking it with me!
That dog is called Kyousuke.
When he heard the bag, he came out.
I'll introduce him to you... to everyone.
Chachan!
Chachan...
My name is Kyousuke.
Yes, Kyousuke.
He came out in response to the sound of the bag.It came out in response to the sound of the bag.
Hey, Shuka.
I always say goodbye to you when I'm in the park.
I don't seem to have time for all that stuff anymore, so bye-bye.
And underwear and pajamas.
I definitely take my pajamas with me.
Even if they were in the hotel.
I have a pair of pajamas that I definitely wear.
This is also a bit of a hobby of mine.
They're a bit tattered.
I can't sleep without them.
I have two kinds of pajamas similar to these.
I can't relax unless I wear it, so I make sure to bring it with me when I stay overnight.
Next...
No, no, no, no!
I'm thinking of wearing a live tee on top of those pajamas.
It's a live tea produced by Momo-chan and me!
The reason we are going to Okinawa this time is because we are going to perform at the Okinawa Collection.
I'm going to perform at the Okinawa Collection.
I'm really grateful for the opportunity, but I'm going to do my own makeup on this day, so I'm bringing my own makeup tools.
As you can see, this is a lunch box.
I'll be doing my makeup there, so I'll bring it with me.
I'm not sure I'll be able to fit one in there, but I'm sure I'll be able to.
I have a straight iron and he has a rigger.
I have a straightening iron and he has a rigger.
This is very expensive.I have a room bureaus.
But I think it's harder to break when I use this iron called a room bureauser.
I think I'm growing out my hair, but I think it's getting really long.
I'd like to grow it longer, but I don't know how to stop it.
I'm trying to stop it with a little bit of a vibe, but it's always coming out.
I'm still trying to figure out how to stop it.
I always try to arrange my hair using hair products, which are very important when doing makeup.
Here are some items for skin care and hair care.
I think I'll take some shampoo.
I use this for both face wash and cleansing.
I also use it to remove point makeup.
I take a lot of things with me.
Various things
What is indispensable for hair care?
I can't live without this brand.
Since I became a blonde, my hair pain has skyrocketed.
So I found this when I couldn't get along with anything else I tried.
I've been using this brand for a while now.
And, well, let's bring an umbrella just in case!
But I think I'm forgetting something.
And last but not least, this pouch. Isn't this pouch so cute?
This is the pouch I usually walk around town in when I go to work or wherever I go.
I don't reapply it during the day, but it doesn't really burn.
Mint tablets, right? Perfume. I can't live without it.
Deodorant. I can't live without it.Deodorant, can't live without it.
And stomach medicine.
The last time I had a stomach ache, I had to leave the house, so I've been carrying this ever since.
There's also disinfectant. Sweat sheets.
Hand cream.
And a good eye wash. Is that it?
I think we're done.
Okay, I'll close.
Okay.
Okay, we're closed!So, I'm going to enjoy Okinawa.
Thank you very much.
Hello everyone!
Chachamaru!
Today we will be packing for Okinawa!
So let's get ready right away!
On the second day, we're going to film a YouTube video by teams.
Yuzu is in the ocean team!
Because we're the ocean team
I wanted to wear a one-piece dress.
I wanted to wear a one-piece dress for the wallpaper shoot.
I already wore a really cute one.
It's my favorite one.
I bought this one today... in the summer.
The last one for the summer.
But I never had a chance to wear it.But you know, I really didn't have a chance to wear it.
I thought for sure I'd get a chance to wear it this time.
How do you like it?
This is my first time in Okinawa.
Have you ever worn it before?
I'm looking forward to seeing how it feels.
I'm already compressing it.
Sorry, you can't see what I'm doing.
These are the clothes.
Look at that.
My milk.It's a carrying case for my milk.
Look.
You know, I bought this on TikTok.
I got it from a TikTok that was getting a lot of attention.
It has a USB port.
It's not bad.
But it doesn't have a USB cord.
I can't put energy into this thing.
It's a coffee maker.
Now that's a great carry-on.
At least I can put my clothes in it.
And...
I think she's going in the pool.
A little bit.
I don't have a bathing suit.I don't have a bathing suit.
It's my mother's.
Here's your bathing suit.
And sandals for the second day.
I didn't have a bag for these either.
A big one.
Oh, yes, yes...
Blanket...
It's gone.
That's why I need a new blanket.
In the winter... when we're touring...
When we tour...I'll definitely bring a blanket.
So I bought one.
Terror pique.
It's so comfy.
It's gonna be on the plane.
I have to do my own makeup this time.
I'll try my best to do it on stage.
Lately I've been into CaroCon.
I'm using this.
That's not how I want to introduce you.
I get it, don't I?
Oh! Fixed.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Anyway...For now.
First, like a selfie stick and phone stand.
Also, put an iron in it and brush your teeth.
Here's some lotion.
Lotion and this.
Face wash, and later put in some makeup remover.
Shampoo, rinse, sweat wipes
Irobon, hair bands
Oh, that reminds me, I need to buy some spray.
Fisheye renu
I don't know what to bring anymore.
Hey, I think the smaller the bag, the better.
I think it's better to put it downUh, but...
Oh, no, can you fit this in there? Here.
Two more boxes.
I'll go with the big one on the second day.
Look what I got recently.
You know what I'm thinking?
I'm going to a concert.
I thought it would be better for a pretty girl.
I'll wear this perfume.
You know... there's a perfume shop at Disney.
Everyone knew there was a perfume shop at Disney.
Yuzu. I like sweet scents.
It says, "The Queen Whispers Sweet Scent.It says "The Queen Whispers Sweet Scents.
It is stored like this.
Well, inside this is a lip
Meg Slip
medicine, mirror, mintia, rubber,
And I also put in this kind of stupid hair cover...
I don't know if it'll fit.
I don't know if it'll fit. Yuzushi, you'll have to do it yourself.
Ribbons and a hair tie, just in case. I'll put in as much as I can.
Look, it's great!
I'm going to enjoy my day in Okinawa.
Okay, I'm going to close now.
Please give us a high rating, click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
Ending
undefined